♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ way down in deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester
and TV's frank ♪
♪ were hatching an
evil scheme ♪
♪ they hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ their experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ so they conked him on the
noggin and they shot him
into space ♪
Get me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can find
la la la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and we'll monitor
his mind la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ where the movies
begin or end la la la ♪
♪ he'll try to
keep his sanity ♪
♪ with the help of
his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call!
♪ Cambot
[show yourself] ♪
♪ Gypsy
[I'm not ready] ♪
♪ Tom Servo
[Hello there] ♪
♪ Crow
[that's one "o"] ♪
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science
facts la la la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really
just relax ♪
♪ for "mystery science
theater 3000" ♪♪
Hi, everybody, your local
Mike Nelson here.
Say, listen, I've programmed
the robots to have different
regional speech patterns.
Okay, I admit it's the only
thing I know how to do, but
still, it should be fun to try
to watch them communicate.
Don't you think?
So crow, before we go to the
show, would y'all like to
have coke?
-Sure, I'll have
a root beer.
-I said coke.
-I know, I'll have
a root beer.
-All I have is coke.
Then forget it,
I'll just use the bubbler.
Huh?
Oh, by the way, what
show are we seeing?
I thought we were
going to a movie.
We are.
-And a show?
-No.
Then why did you say
we're going to a show?
Because we are.
-What show?
-"Awakenings."
That's a movie.
I know!
-Are you going
to come with?
-Come with what?
Me, crow, me!
Are you going to
come with me?
Yeah, but I'm a little low.
Could you borrow
me some money?
Wait a minute, okay,
I think that's enough.
You know, there's a difference
between regionalism and just
plain stupidity.
But Mike, irregardless
of that fact...
♪♪
So what time's dinner?
Is noon okay?
But that's lunch!
Lunch, dinner, same thing.
Oh, something's flashing
over to the what's-it area.
Ooh, the blinker!
Ah yeah.
Mike.
Oh.
What time is it?
I slept late.
I have an experiment for
you around here somewhere.
Frank, where's the matter
transference device?
I didn't use it
last, Clay.
Oh, uh, here it is.
Well, this little device allows
you to break down molecular
patterns
and reassemble them
again elsewhere.
I haven't gotten all the bugs
worked out of it yet.
Thought I'd try
it out on you.
You know, there's
a bit of an ion storm.
Are you sure you should be
sending that right now?
Nonsense.
What could
possibly go wrong?
So we're not gonna do any
experiment that messes with
the laws of nature.
You try your little matter
transference device out on
your own self.
Yeah, you're just lucky nothing
happened sending it up there
in an ion storm.
Oh yeah, what he said.
What in the world?
You failed to properly
compensate during the ion storm.
Your agonizer, please.
But captain Mike--
your agonizer, please.
Agonizer, agonize.
Where the heck did
I put that doo-hickey?
It's right there
on your belt.
No, no, that's not it.
-It is too.
-Nope.
-I remember I had it--
-would you just give me your
agonizer, please?
For crying out loud, you're
supposed to keep fresh batteries
in your agonizer at all times.
-I don't know what happened,
-i-- oh, that's just great.
Let's just go to
the agony booth.
Please.
It is not.
Tom! What's happened?
What's wrong with
Mike and crow?
Uh, what do you mean?
I mean, they're
all evil and stuff.
Really?
I hadn't noticed.
Don't you think it's just a
little weird that we're down
here in deep 13?
That is weird.
Still, I suppose they
do that kind of thing.
Tom, it seems as though the ion
storm sent us into an evil
parallel dimension.
Our lives are at stake.
We can't trust anyone.
Well, okay, let's try
to make the best of it.
Oh, typical.
The agony booth is
out of order.
You can call those service
people and they'll be around,
oh, say, December, maybe.
Well, I could
bring it out--
shut up, yeoman crow.
-Shutting up.
-Thank you.
Your movie today is a little
western called "the last of the
wild horses" that I like to
think smells like the inside
of John Goodman's chaps.
Yippee-die-yi-yay!
Shut up.
And this one here is
the eight of Chris lemon...
Will you look at that?
We've got movie sign!
Go, go!
[Announcer]
"Last of the wild horses."
Aren't you going to carry
me into the theater?
Frank, you're getting
too big for that.
Oh, it's my favorite part.
Just watch the show.
I have that
sciatic nerve.
[Announcer]
This is the rogue river
valley in southern Oregon,
-famous for its scenic
and historical landmarks.
-Like dirt and stuff.
[Announcer] Oregon's first
settlers stopped here and built
one of the oldest settlements.
Then they moved on.
[Announcer] ...Whose original
buildings still stand as when
they were built nearly
a century ago.
Wow.
[Announcer] The entire action of
this picture was filmed in
beautiful rogue
river valley and in
Jacksonville, one of the few
remaining true western towns.
So even though the
movie sucks, they still...
Can't stress that
enough, folks.
"Last of the wild horses."
Frazee!
With these people and plenty
of vitamins and minerals.
You lost the last of
the wild horses, you dink.
Oh, Albert glasser, the man who
holds you down and pummels you
with music.
I wonder what day Albert
glasser wrote this score.
Two curlys fighting
for supremacy.
I would date
yolanda molinari.
She seems nice.
"My life as a dog,"
the western version.
I never wanted to do
summerstock in the first place.
Oh yeah, the hittleman film
empire began with this movie.
Let's save our strength.
We'll probably have to fight
later in the movie.
-Oh.
Little Joe and Adam
have it out.
Hey, I have
leather contacts!
You rarely see
a good facial whipping.
...first place,
barnum.
Now I'm going
to finish you.
Journey to the
beginning of time!
Scrubbing bubbles, scrubbing
bubbles, ooh hoo hoo!
Hey, he's dressed
like a cossack.
What is that about?
I'm not moving here.
Look at all the people.
Ew, smells like
grandma's purse.
Ew.
It's the bazooka Joe guy.
Hey, I had dibs.
Down, down, boy.
Shoo, go home!
Looks like kind of
a one-sided caper.
You're good, boss.
Well, it's none
of my business.
I don't even know
who I am yet!
I hope it's not the three
amigos, 'cause I'd like
a comedy.
Oh, man, a great
big juicy stagecoach!
Oh, I'm getting horsesick.
I hope you know that these
are billable hours, boss.
Boss, you care
too much!
Damn you!
No, stay,
go home, go home.
Go.
Judy, freckles?
No, go home.
No use hanging on to that
artillery any longer.
Might as well get
rid of it.
See your license, please?
I mean now.
Oh yeah, their three guns are
probably useless against
his one.
What are you
butting in for?
Three against one isn't exactly
my idea of the right odds.
I don't know who you are, but
you're not gonna get away
with this.
I'm a bunny.
There's a law about aiding
and abetting a horse thief.
Oh, well, now, why didn't
somebody tell me?
Far be it for me
to break the law.
He's being facetious,
isn't he?
I thought he was an honest
citizen and you fellas were
breaking the law.
Apparently sarcasm hasn't
hit the old west yet.
I guess he must be
over the hill by now.
No use chasing him.
Might as well call
the whole thing off.
-To-mah-to!
-To-may-to!
Beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep.
Still got it.
Vroom, vroom, vroom!
Oh, god, that stang!
Way to go, Ted.
Now we have to
talk to him again.
Please, sir, can we
have our bullets back?
Ought to be a law against a man
carrying a concealed weapon.
You boys get
tempted too easy.
Get down.
This is very awkward, 'cause
all of the horses are really
good friends.
Very embarrassing.
Now line dance!
Take 'em off or
I'll burn 'em off.
Ask him if you can show him
something in a nubuck pump.
Let me help
you here, Gary.
You have those hammertoes.
Foot fetishists
of the old west.
Now say you're gonna check
in back for a size five!
Drop 'em!
Did I say throw them?
Now do it again.
They're all wearing
white clogs.
Hey, you've
got webbed toes.
I miss my spur noises.
Jacksonville, where church,
family and hopefully someday
industry come together!
Great big backs
of the old west.
Oh no, he just hit
a pedestrian.
I'm so sick of
gingham I could scream!
Ha ha, I love my job.
We were almost held
up over near the pass.
What do you mean, almost?
I'm carrying
a big shipment.
I wasn't taking
any chances.
I was watching the road ahead
about half a mile and I seen
this masked feller.
By the time we got around the
bend, he was gone.
All right, we'll try
and round him up.
Get the horses, Chuck.
What'd he look like, Tom?
Oh, he was a big fella.
His own horse,
had a black bandana.
Beautiful thighs.
That's good enough for
me, see you later.
Nice tummy.
Well Mrs. Bixby
and Mrs. Jones.
Now look, everything's
gonna be all right.
Mrs. Bixby.
Break it up, folks,
break it up.
Go on home and
disappoint your husbands.
Ew, look at
the all the poo.
Oh, one of my
tires is low.
I will not let you
not buy this shoe.
Cut it out, that tickles!
I wasn't playing
shoe store!
His horse has the look of
someone who's spent a lot
of time humoring his master.
-Hello there.
-Hello there!
I just had
a little trouble.
My horse threw a shoe.
Ate a ringer.
That's too bad.
I think you can get him
reshod up at the ranch.
Which ranch?
-Double c.
-Oh, that's fine.
Where is it?
What an idiot.
You're on it.
Covers practically
the entire valley.
And most the world!
Ranch house is up over
the next hill about a mile.
Thanks.
Say, it's lucky for me
you happened along.
Otherwise, I might
have had to walk.
I got news for you.
You're still gonna walk.
Ooh, yippee-yi-youch!
Oh, good one, boss.
Maybe I could just hold on to
your horse's tail and you
could drag me or someth--
I don't know.
The double cranch?
What is that about?
It's a sprawling studio
apartment ranch.
What'd Jane bring
home with her now?
How do you like
this one, dad?
-Hello dad.
-Hello dear!
Think you can
fix him up?
Why, sure we can have
a shoe for his horse.
Got more shoes
than we have horses.
Dad's mental.
One horse... hey, slim.
Throw a shoe on
this fella's horse.
Thanks.
You look like you could stand
something cool and wet.
Dad!
So could my feet.
Get his feet
a glass of lemonade.
Well, don't just
stand there, go get us a drink.
Yes, dad.
[Vocalizes]
I like the property you
got around here.
Real dysfunctional.
Yeah, built it
all up myself.
Started from scratch with
a brood of wild mares.
Never would stop expanding
if it hadn't been for this.
Now I'm expanded.
Ha!
Stampede one night,
bust myself up good.
Ever since then, I turned over
most of the management to Riley.
That's nice.
Where's your daughter?
Must be a lot of wild horses
in this part of the country.
No, no.
-His doppelganger.
-Huh.
Trouble?
From the small
ranch owners.
They claim that
we're the cause of it.
That we were taking too many
mares from the herd.
Let them claim
whatever they want!
Yeah! Tourettes
of the old west.
-They don't like--
-looks like you're the one that
could use something cool now.
Hi, I'm Susan.
I'll be your
daughter today.
Oh, quit giving me pee.
♪♪
Curly and anti-curly.
Afternoon, miss Jane.
Mr. Cooper, Riley.
Well, sheriff,
what brings you here?
Oh, I'm trying to pick
up a fella's trail.
The west palm stage just
pulled into Jacksonville
a little while ago
and reported seeing a masked
man down near the pass.
Sit down, sheriff.
Thanks, Jane.
That's a long sentence and
you're probably tried.
Howdy.
Stage held up?
No.
We had a couple extra guards
planted in the coach.
The guard riding on the seat
was watching the road ahead
for about a half mile
through field glasses.
Fascinating.
By the time they got to the
pass, the masked man had gone.
It's me!
It's me.
I sure would have liked to have
seen the look on that fella's
face if he'd have tried to
stick up that stage.
The joke is on
the sheriff.
Did the guard get
a good look at him?
Yeah.
Good as you could a half mile
away through field glasses.
Said he was big.
Wearing a black bandana for a
mask and riding a roan horse.
Actually, my scarf is dark
Navy and so is my horse.
I don't envy you
or your job, sheriff.
This country must be full of big
fellas wearing black bandanas
and riding roan horses.
Everyone here is so fun.
Ah, not so many.
Say, you got a sweet
outlaw ass, don't you?
You're big.
Unless I'm mistaken, that's a
black bandana you're wearing.
They are falling
for each other hard.
What color horse was
this man riding, Mr. Cooper?
It was just a head
and a stick!
It was weird!
Roan.
I can explain,
it was a loaner roan!
Something's wrong, sheriff.
I wasn't near the pass.
I came up through
the valley.
Let's go barefoot
all summer!
That's just me.
I gotta have an arch
support and a firm...
Give me your gun.
Well, they'll do
that sometimes.
Well, I guess my horse
ought to be shod by now.
-Thanks a lot, Mr. Cooper, i--
-freeze.
Oh, they're
playing freeze tag.
What's this all
about, rocky?
After he shot Hank, he made us
get off our horses, stampede 'em
and then took our guns.
Took your boots
too, I see.
Shut up, Iris.
What have you got
to say for yourself?
Part of what he
says is right.
The other part
is right too.
I just thought I'd delay them a
little and give the kid a break
when he took a shot at me.
I'm so lost.
...prevent anyone
from getting hurt.
I don't like any unnecessary
gunplay going on in my
jurisdiction.
You're gonna have to answer
to a charge of assault.
Besides, this places you down
at the pass, which is another
little matter I want to get
cleaned up.
Let's go,
put it away, rocky.
Yeah and we're gonna pin the
cattle rustling from last year
on you too if you don't mind.
He's wearing chick jeans.
They fit better.
He drank our
apple juice.
We didn't get close enough
to tell for sure.
I suppose you took
a couple of pot shots at him.
Well, yes, but we only tried
to put a scare into him.
Haven't we got enough trouble
in this valley without my men
making more?
No.
Riley, get him out of my sight
before I have him thrown off
the ranch.
I warned you before, rocky,
about being trigger happy.
I want to talk to you.
Glad we had this little
face-to-groin talk.
I told you to be careful
whenever you made a move.
Next time you go after anyone,
be sure there are no witnesses
around.
This fella came
out of nowhere.
Well, watch your
step from now on.
Things are going
too good to spoil.
I got the old man so
he won't budge.
I put a rock
behind his wheel.
I want you to push the small
ranches around until they won't
take anymore.
When they're pushed too far,
this whole valley will bust
loose.
When that happens,
where do we stand?
On the sideline.
What's a sideline, sir?
When they do, we'll bring
the law down on them.
And as they're wiped
out, I'll take over.
Suppose old man Cooper's got
his own idea about all this?
When I get through with him,
he'll see things my way or else.
Why did they
hire hoyt axton?
Because you got brawn where
your brains ought to be.
You stick with me and you'll
be wearing gold bullets.
Where?
In my belt or
in my back?
Why, if this scene
wasn't ending, i'd--
bless your beautiful hide
they need to invent the
stoplight.
Remedy.
There he is!
Stop the music.
Retail space for rent.
-See?
-Hmm.
This town has
a real western theme.
Mmm.
I'm going to crabtree
and Evelyn.
I'm strangely drawn--
the magnetic pull is
too strong-- oh!
Want to go have a beer
before I book you?
I like to greet them at the door
wearing nothing but this.
What's the charge?
Oh, the charge?
Assault with
intent to kill.
He shot Hank Davis, one
of the double c boys.
That's right.
Me and Terry as right there,
saw the whole thing.
It was self-defense.
Hank drew first and fired before
he even got his gun out.
Hank fired four shots.
Two.
Sounded like four to me.
Oh, forget it,
you weren't there.
Having trouble
with my ears lately.
Yeah, it's a rare ailment
known as double hearing.
-Just like--
-you're not going to be in
this movie, are you?
...fix up some of that
ear remedy when he gets back
to the ranch.
We'll testify to that
at the trial, sheriff.
Your word's all right
with me, remedy.
Even though
you're mental.
I guess that sort of clears you
of the shooting, doesn't it?
Thank you.
I'm going to hold you
on another charge.
What kind of a charge?
Suspicion.
That description of the masked
man waiting to hold up the stage
fits you pretty well.
He ain't the man you're
looking for, sheriff.
He was with us every
minute of the day.
Wasn't he, Terry?
Never left my sight
for a second.
Why, he's no more a crook
than you are, sheriff.
Why, he's a new ranch hand
I hired the other day.
Well, I guess that clears you
all the way around, doesn't it?
It's easygoing justice
'round these here parts.
Yep.
Thanks, pal.
Hey, remedy?
Yeah?
I want to talk
to you a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, this is gonna
be great!
Can I show you something
in a slip-on?
Maybe open toed?
Something sensible,
nothing too...
I just want to remind you that
you were right here when the
stage pulled in and
reported the whole thing.
Me?
You must be suffering with
that double vision I was
talking about.
If you are, I got
a remedy for it.
Ow, my trick nipple!
I'll tell you what
I'm willing to do.
I'm willing to place him in your
custody until I'm satisfied one
way or the other.
Aw, he'll come through
a third way...
God love the
drunken old fart.
Hey, they got in
a shipment of Muslim women.
That makes us even.
Quite a kid
you got there.
Plenty of nerve.
Plenty of what it takes
to ride a horse too.
Harassment!
Well, what do you know?
A little tomboy.
-Say, if I'd known that,
I wouldn't have smacked--
-i tell her a hundred times if
she's gonna go around dressed
like a boy gotta learn to
take it like a boy.
Oh.
Barnum, Duke barnum.
I think.
Well, I guess
I better take off.
-Take off?
-Yeah.
I've got sort of
a date over at Quincy.
I'm opening a shoe
store there.
Maybe.
So long, remedy.
Oh, it ain't
gonna be so long.
As far as i'm
concerned, it is.
But you're supposed to
be our new ranch hand.
Oh, you made
a mistake.
But you're my
love interest.
Maybe I better go tell
the sheriff he ain't the man
I hired the other day.
Yeah, must have been
a case of mistaken identity.
Yeah.
Funny though, he looks
just like--
everybody wants
a piece of the Duke.
You got a bad
memory for faces.
Who are you?
Better take
another look.
Am I the fella that
remedy hired or not?
You're the jerk that
smacked my butt.
Oh, we gotta go.
Let's go.
[Both talking at once]
Hey, I've got this puppet.
Let's do a song
about the lemur!
Okay.
♪ Joey the lemur the
friend to mankind ♪
♪ a furry kind of monkey
friend he really does shine ♪
♪ Joey the lemur he's
great to have around ♪
Oh, this is worse
than I ever
imagined having my worst
nightmare about!
This is horrible!
There are no lemurs
in this movie!
♪ The lemur the
kind of animal ♪
♪ that would go
to the bathroom ♪
Now, now, wait a minute.
It's the lemur--
I order you let me go!
Traitorous pigs!
What's going on?
Where's my personal guard?
Oh, oh.
Oh, right, Mike.
Whatever your game is,
I'll play it.
Apparently some sort of
transposition has taken place.
Extremely
interesting, plankton.
I have no idea why
I said that.
Anyway, we gotta get
him inside the theater.
What is it that
will buy you?
Power? I can get
that for you.
Money? Credit?
Name it!
♪♪
Let me go!
I'll have you killed,
then tortured!
Oh, hey,
a cowboy movie.
Sit and watch it.
What are you studying?
Oh, just a little
of everything.
Cure anybody of anything.
Man or beast.
Medicine.
Chiropracticry.
Veterinarian.
Victoria's secret?
Now I can pull that tooth
that's been bothering curly.
My butter shipment.
No, the cook.
Don't tell me you're studying
to be a dentist too.
Why, you got
a toothache?
No thanks.
I want to be a dentist.
Sure there's nothing
wrong with you?
No.
I'm just
disgustingly healthy.
And I'm not gay.
Hey, it's a drug
deal going down.
I'll be with you
in a few minutes.
I've got a little unfinished
business to take care of.
I, uh, need to
get really drunk.
...looking for trouble.
I won't go out
of my way.
Wow, this place is crawling
with Holly hobbies.
What kind of drink specials
they got in there, partner?
Hi.
I want to correct something
you said at the double c
a while ago.
You used
a double negative.
I never shot a man
in the back.
-Kidneys, sure, but...
-Gonna give you a chance
to eat those words.
Hey, the two o'clock
shoot-out's starting!
Could we have some
privacy please?
Never thought
of that.
I hope this doesn't ruin the
taste of Jacksonville festival.
I'm gonna give you
a chance to draw first.
Sale at penney's!
Wow, the amish are
really hauling ass!
Lumpiest couple of
cowboys I've ever seen.
As my legal representative,
what would you recommend?
So, uh, what are
you gonna do now?
Well?
All right.
Have your way, baby.
As far as I know, you never
shot anyone in the back.
Well, thank you,
that's all I wanted.
That's better.
That's worse!
Drop it!
Wow!
Pistol-packing mama!
Saved by a girl.
You scuffed my
hair, you dink.
He's wearing Adam
ant's shirt.
Should have known better
than turn my back!
I've learned an
invaluable life lesson.
Always gathering
for fights.
How do they ever get
any shopping done?
Handy with
his Dukes too.
Maybe that's how
he got his name.
His name is handy?
Town of Carrie nations.
This is like gamera versus
zigra, only with cowboys.
Right.
Cool, he almost made
it into his hat!
Break it up, break it up.
Get up...
There's a law in this town
against disturbing the peace.
-You got a lot of
laws around here.
-I'll say.
And I aim to see you
don't break any.
Come on, you.
This is a pretty
wimpy old west.
It's more like the midwest
part of the old west.
Like Des Moines.
Remedy's other
nickname is ow!
What a beautiful cut.
Have you ever
thought of a perm?
'Course, I could probably done
the job with only two stitches.
No use taking chances.
No.
'Sides, you needed
the practice.
Get your greasy
thumb out of there.
Look too.
You know, I could
hardly see it.
Wouldn't know I'd done it
myself if I hadn't done it.
Well, is he all
right, remedy?
He'll be able to think
in a month or so.
He got a fever?
No, but I think
you have.
Remedy, soon to be
known as malpractice.
Quite a girl you
got there.
Here, take her
for a drive.
She was sort of left to me
when my partner passed about
15 years ago.
Oh, I see.
I'm strictly
a bachelor.
I know when I'm well off.
I've been trapped by this
guy at so many parties.
I don't see why you
dragged me out here.
From the size of this place,
looks like you could run it with
the help you've already got.
I know it ain't
a very big place.
-But I sort of figured if
you was handy with horses--
-hey, what's he looking at?
...you might get
to like it.
Stick around to raise horses
instead of sticking up
stagecoaches.
I need some alone
time right now.
What makes you think I want
to make a career of it?
Just a dilettante.
How many you
stuck up so far?
Oh.
Not counting the one
I started today, none.
I thought so.
You're right purdy.
...stuck your neck out
the way you did this morning.
Oh, here comes wacky,
nutty chaos!
Oh, my comic
relief shift is over.
-Og oggilby ...
-Curly?
Oh, even smoke
hurts this tooth.
That's what you get for
eating your own cooking.
Why don't you blow it out--
oh, remedy.
Open your mouth.
Oh, it's only
a shoehorn.
Open your mouth.
Wider.
Here's your problem.
You got a tongue
stuck in here.
There it is.
The third bicuspid.
No it ain't.
It's my tooth.
Now my mouth
tastes like your foot.
Well, just disinfect this
by wiping it in my armpit.
Rochester.
What a nice picture.
Oh.
Oh, I'm all
full of nits!
Spiders!
Yes, sir, curly.
To chew everything,
you got to through with it.
There's devils inside you.
What's the root of all this
horse trouble in the valley,
remedy?
Lack of horses.
Had to come sooner
or later, I guess.
Just taking the mares away from
a wild herd and pretty soon,
there's no more herd.
-What's the solution?
-Saline.
Well, in the lumber country when
the forests start to go bad,
they stop cutting
trees for a while.
That's what they
gotta do here.
Stop rounding up horses.
Maybe a year or two.
Give the herd
a chance to grow.
Look, I'll pull
my tooth.
Everybody in
favor of this?
-Everybody but the double c.
-Charlie Cooper?
He can stand one bad year
better than us little fellas.
So far he's been
stubborn as a mule.
I'm afraid if he won't listen to
reason, trouble's gonna go a lot
deeper than just bad...
Now, let's get
that appendix out!
Too bad.
Ain't they
beauties, curly?
Oh.
Brand-new,
never been used before.
Oh.
Are they allowed to have two
comedy people in this movie?
Guess I better look up the
literature on how to use them.
No, just wasting time.
Just yank till
something gives.
Open your mouth.
Hmm-mm!
Come on, open your mouth.
Is it safe?
Wow.
Frontier dental
hygienists.
Ah!
My epiglottis!
Dances with, uh,
something, I'm not sure.
Are we supposed
to find our smile?
We're file clerks, what the
hell are we doing on horses?
[Vocalizes]
Bonanza!
"Bonanza" starring
the mandrel sisters.
They don't seem wild.
They seem more
fancy-free.
The double c don't let a day go
by without raiding the herd.
I still like this movie
better than "Silverado."
Is this is the legend of
curly Joe derita's gold?
The three tri-captains meet for
the coin toss in the middle
of the field.
Wild herd or are they
the double c stock?
-The answer is yes
to both questions.
-To you, Arlene Francis.
If you fellas don't lay off that
herd for a while, there isn't
going to be any herd.
-That's what I heard.
-You make it a habit of
butting into everything
that's not your
business, don't you?
-Butt.
Maybe I'll make it my
business from now on.
We take our orders
from Mr. Cooper.
If he wants horses,
we round 'em up.
If you don't like it,
take it up with him.
Middle-management
of the old west.
Okay, see you
at card club then.
-This thing has got to be
brought to a head once--
-and popped!
♪♪
That was a fun day.
Hello, Jane.
Hello, sheriff.
-Hello...
-Hello, Steve.
I had some visitors
this morning.
We just painted
that three.
Delegation from
the other ranchers.
They want to know once and for
all if you're gonna lay off that
wild herd for a year.
What I said still goes.
Nobody's gonna tell me when
I can and can't run horses.
Dad, did you need
to yell at me again?
I guess that's
final then.
-That's final.
-Is it final?
-All right, Mr. Cooper.
-It's final.
But I'm warning you, I won't be
responsible for what happens.
You know I only
got one deputy.
You got a lot of ranchers.
I'll protect my own range.
I've got guns and
I've got the men too.
Is that the only way you know
how to settle things, with guns?
Shut up, Iris.
-Those ranchers are
right and you know it.
-I tell you, shut up.
But rather than sacrifice
anything, you'll turn against
men who are your neighbors.
You will shoot and kill men who
once were your friends just to
assert your will and your power.
She speaks for all
women everywhere.
...but remember, you turn
them against you turn me too.
Just for that, I'm not going to
let you feed me or help me with
my ablutions.
I do like stuffing
more than potatoes.
Tell them the double c won't
run any horses for a year.
-Excuse me, I'm sorry,
I didn't catch--
-I'll notify Riley and the boys.
-I'm sorry, the sound
of the music is--
-i didn't-- oh, crap.
And now Robert lippord
pretends he's John Ford.
I think she may be
doing that wrong.
She has no idea how delightful
her life's about to become.
Jeez, I should have
looked the other way.
Hi.
It's me.
Her shorts should be shorter
or her pants could be longer.
Kind of grunge.
Oh oh, sat on the
saddle horn there.
-Hello there.
-Hello dere!
My horse is trying
to jump fences.
He took the last jump without
the saddle and I happened to
be in it.
She can really
tell a story, huh?
Good thing you came along or
I probably would have had--
oh oh oh.
Oh ho ho.
You can't.
Why not?
--You made me walk.
Payback time.
But I don't know why I did it
and I felt awfully bad about it
afterwards.
You felt bad about it?
I have a couple blisters
to prove how I felt.
Wanna see 'em?
Guess I can't
blame you.
And to think, I was going
to have sex with you.
-Hey, wait a minute.
-Yes?
I want to see you crawl.
And your gaucho
pants, come on.
Your feet hurt yet?
How's it feel?
Keep walking, sister!
Feel every
blister I felt!
I like you.
I knew you were
a gentleman.
I've been accused of everything
since I hit this part of
the country.
Shot Kennedy according
to some folks.
Okay, your honor.
What's the sentence?
Hey, look at that idiot over
there with the saddle.
Oh, rush hour.
Sundown slowdown.
You know, it's funny.
-Ha ha!
-What?
...come back into
the valley again.
Want to drive
for a while?
A year's going to make a lot
of difference in that herd.
Your father did the right thing
when he came to terms with the
other ranchers.
I wish I could make
him see that.
Even though he did give in, I
still feel he regrets doing it.
That's too bad.
If he doesn't keep faith, the
whole thing's liable to blow
right open again.
Don't worry about dad.
Once he's given his word,
he'll keep it.
That's good.
That was a great scene.
Oh, back to
the main scene.
Oh, my head.
Yeah, thanks
for the help.
I've only been getting off
horses since I was five.
I'm a formula
one racecar.
Vroom, vroom!
He's not going to tell any of
those weird-ass jokes, is he?
...only got one
horse between you.
What became
of the filly?
I just saw her
in the corral.
She decided to come
home without me.
Why don't you
grab a shave?
-Thanks for the lift.
-Don't mention it.
Next time,
it'll be your turn.
Well, have you been beating up
or shooting any more of my help
lately?
None today.
So far.
I hear that fight you
had in town was a honey.
I used to be able to handle
myself pretty good too when
I was your age.
I bet you could.
Can I look under
your blanket?
Jane tells me you're not
too happy with the deal on
the horses.
You're darn
right I'm not.
-Yeah!
-Wow.
If it hadn't been for her,
I wouldn't have gotten into it.
Do you realize what one year's
inactivity's going to do to the
double c?
Well, it's gonna cost the
little fella something too.
-But in the end, you'll--
-it's a talking wheelchair!
Don Adams, eavesdropper.
Glad to hear
you say that.
Otherwise, there
might be a fight.
Every time they have fun,
they never invite me.
I thought they'd be planning
my surprise party, but no.
Wow, he's black crow
lead singer thin.
Rocky.
Yeah?
I want you to
find my butt.
What?
I want you to round up every
wild horse in the valley.
Are you kidding?
There's hundreds of them
between here and the mountains.
Besides, we haven't
got enough men.
I know that.
You'll have to take whatever men
we can spare from here and pick
up the rest out on the range.
You understand?
I definitely kind
of understand.
You know, if we do that, it'll
be the last of the wild horses.
And there'll be no need for
Arthur Miller's misfits.
Now, my butt.
My butt.
Had it at church.
Look at those guys,
they got butts.
I'm sitting
on my pelvis.
No flesh there
or anything.
His scalp ever seen
a bar of soap?
Not bad.
I'm sure I can lose the
weight before the wedding.
Not bad at all.
I think Terry's
gonna like it.
It feels kind of tight.
That's okay.
Terry ain't
as big as you.
She's bigger
in some places.
Two grown men,
ladies and gentlemen.
You know, I think
I'm going to have...
Time on my hands over
the next two years.
I think I'll take
up dressmaking by mail.
How come Terry decided she
wanted to dress like a girl
all of a sudden?
She's a girl,
ain't she?
Yeah, sure, but how come she
just got conscious of it?
What makes a girl
realize she's a girl?
A man.
I want this scene
to go away.
Thank you.
Things are going to be pretty
quiet for a while around the
ranch now that everybody's
stopped rounding up horses.
I've just been thinking
about the same thing.
You visualize
buck Owens?
I don't know.
Remedy wants me to.
Then you'll stay.
Remedy says he can make anybody
do anything he wants them to.
Actors, please stay in
the reflector light.
Do you have a girl?
No, got me a horse.
Oh, sure.
Uh, what's a girl?
What's she like?
Uh, which one?
Which one?
You mean you have
more than one?
Oh, no, that is, not more
than one in each town.
[Together]
Liar!
Get two girls together...
You know how women talk.
I'll never forget the one in
El Paso...Or was it Albuquerque?
-Anyway, when these two girls--
-oh, I think you're terrible.
Why, thank you.
Here we go.
Philandering bastards
of the old west.
Movie's just
starting to mosey now.
♪♪
Jeez, Mike, Servo's gotten
really weird and gypsy is too.
Yeah, I know, I'm afraid
we've lost them to an
alternate universe.
Yeah, that'll happen.
Suppose we ought
to do something, huh?
Yeah.
Of course we should
do something.
Unfortunately, I saved my
alternate universe manual
from college.
You went to college?
-Well, actually, it was a
vo-tech, but still, the manual--
-we better go get it quick!
It's a dangerous
game we play, Tom Servo.
You mean like jarts?
No, you fool.
I mean power.
Ultimate power.
Oh yeah, right.
The power to rule
the galaxies, it's ours.
Yours and mine
for the taking.
No kidding? Wow.
Are you man enough
to take command?
Oh yeah.
I suppose.
Are you sure?
Well, I don't
know if I...
Come here.
And let me make a man out
of you, captain Servo.
Oh wow.
Oh, jeez, look, it's movie
time, honey, gotta go!
I will be
a captive woman.
Boy, that gypsy is one
sexy mama, isn't she?
Chances are, they'll
be watching the pass.
Drive the herd
toward the double c.
Double c, I thought it
was the double cranch.
Don't worry, I will.
Here's a curling iron.
Drop this where they'll
be sure to find it.
I want you to brand
Carol Channing.
Good talking
to you, Ernie.
Always a pleasure.
Oh boy, I'm galloping!
No need to hit me!
Occasionally, you'll see one
of them horses at spago at
the wrap parties.
There they are.
-Without you,
Gary, we'd be lost.
-That's them.
All right, men, if it's only
the herd, don't bother 'em.
But if there's any riders,
you know what to do.
Actually,
we don't, sir.
Sir?
You see, this is where the
sepia tone really pays off.
Drink in the
lush photography.
Hey, mind your
space cushion.
Here they come.
They showed that clip at the
academy awards when that guy
was nominated for best actor.
On top of everything else,
they're litterers.
Hey, the horses
don't have guns.
They're quakers,
you bastards!
Pop, pop, pop, pop.
Bow, bow, bow, bow.
Boo-doo-daw.
Another Chuck and m80s.
Ah.
And then it just
sort of Peters out.
Spotted any of
those riders?
[Speaks gibberish]
Come on, we're going
down to the double c.
Wait a minute.
You haven't any proof it was the
double c men other than the word
of some drunk.
He might have just been
shooting off his mouth.
That's right, I'd hate to
see us make a move without
some kind of proof.
So would I, but-- hey, Ferguson,
look what I found in the Meadow.
The double c
branding iron.
Convinced now?
This settles it,
let's go.
So their whole plan is
based on dumb luck.
Whoa, Phil, you flamed
out your horse!
Hop sing is
making chow mein.
This is a gripping
Levi's commercial.
♪ Hi ho hi ho it's off
to work we go... ♪♪
We've come a-courting.
Delivering their
funds a-popping.
Hello, Mr. Ferguson.
We'd like to see
your father, Jane.
Jane? Who is it?
Ferguson, dad.
Oh, hello, Pete.
-Pow!
-Hello boys.
Old man, your picante sauce
is made in New York City!
I guess so.
Got double c on it.
It was found down
in the Meadow.
I guess one of the
boys was careless.
Very careless.
-Wow, that's like
a whole foot of ear.
-What are you driving at?
That iron was found down in the
Meadow after some riders drove
a band of wild horses through.
This is about me,
isn't it?
You're not insinuating
we've been raiding the herd?
We're not insinuating
anything, Charlie,
we're just taking facts.
Why, that branding iron might
have been lost a week ago,
a month ago, any time.
That's possible.
In that case, you won't object
to our looking over your stock.
You're darn
right I object.
-Wow.
-You keep out of this.
Sorry for lending
my support.
-I told you, the double c hasn't
been raiding the wild horses.
-Double cranch.
...won't have anybody inspect
my stock to check up on my word.
The whole thing's beginning
to look like a frame-up.
I wouldn't be surprised if one
of you fellas was backing the
whole thing in order to break up
the agreement.
If that's the way you want it,
that's all right with me.
You better think
this over, Mr. Cooper.
I have thought it over.
I'm giving orders any
trespassers on the double c
be shot on sight.
Mr. Cooper, you're only buying
yourself a lot of trouble.
I can pay for
anything I buy.
Na na na na.
Kindergarten baby,
wash your face in gravy,
wrap it up in bubblegum
and send it to the Navy.
Nyah.
Hey, come on,
I was kidding.
Hey, wait!
They still had to
pay for parking.
The double cranch
does not validate.
They've left me
no other choice.
Please, Jane!
Get the doomsday
machine!
-Riley.
-I wasn't listening!
He's the George
stephanopoulos of the ranch.
-Snuffleupagus?
-George snuffleupagus.
I've just told Pete Ferguson and
the boys that any trespassers at
the double c will be shot.
-[Speaks gibberish]
-Why not let the
sheriff handle it?
Those are orders, Riley.
Then if they come on your
range, you'll have the law
on your side.
You'll be entitled
to protection.
Once again,
I'm putty in your hands.
Over here.
I guess I lost my head.
Maybe that's the best
way to handle it.
John waters,
Texas ranger.
For a while last night,
it looked as if the whole thing
would bust wide open.
I had a feeling it
wasn't going to last.
That was a great
brunch, though.
Protection.
All right, I'll round up
some men and swear them in.
You won't have to
look for any deputies.
My rotisserie baseball.
Let's see.
"Dear sheriff, I like you,
do you like me?
Check one." Hmm.
These are all
double c men.
Double semen!
Don't touch me.
We're picking our
own deputies.
Not while I'm sheriff.
Wait, I'll be right up
there and then I'll retort.
Maybe we can do
something about that too.
I'd love to bite the
bridge of your nose.
Are you forgetting that
Cooper put you in this job?
Al d'amatos of
the old west.
Well, what's
it gonna be?
Our deputies or your job?
So, is that the end of the
scene or do you have another--
no, that's it.
Okay.
Now remember,
you're deputies.
What? Thank you.
No matter what you do,
you got the law on your side.
And if someone should
accidentally be killed
while resisting arrest,
-that's too bad.
-Huh? Huh? Get it?
Kill guys!
Can we do anything, sir?
Can we burn puppies?
Maybe this will come in handy
to settle some personal affairs?
Now there's a man who
understands me, thank you.
Now go do that voodoo
that you do so well!
We got the law
on our side.
I'm gonna fail
to yield!
Give it up
for my posse.
Guys, it's not as much fun
as I thought it would be.
Hey, don't push,
I'm going.
Now, fly,
my horsies, fly!
Not leaving. Just because
the rest of you are doing it,
I don't have to.
Let's all go to
ft. Lauderdale!
Ooh, blew a tire.
Uh, I don't think you're
supposed to burn your own barn,
Ted.
Well, quick cup of Joe,
then back at it.
[Imitates flatulence]
-Hey.
-It's funny.
What do you want here?
Just checking your horses to see
if there's any double c brand in
your corral.
Get off my place.
There's no double c
horses in my corral.
Then maybe you wouldn't mind
doing me the service of dying!
You're getting
double c horses now.
If you were alive, you'd
hear that ironic retort.
The tonton macoutes
of the old west.
Old timer,
Billy slater, no!
No, I don't wanna
live with grandma.
This guy wouldn't even be
a greeter at Roy Rogers.
Hey, he transmogrified.
He's thinner.
"Never liked him,"
neighbor declares.
Building code
invented and under fire.
At least there's
no art buchwald.
[Vocalizing]
Word "exonerated"
is invented.
Literacy rate rises
to one percent.
Look at that,
the orcs are involved.
Siamese horses!
-Dan Rowan and dick Martin
in "once upon a horse."
-That was a great movie.
Wasn't it "once upon..."
You guys, we have
the whole prairie.
Do we have to
bunch up like this?
How many of you already
know about amway?
Remedy and I got
word to join you.
[Vocalizes]
Howdy Hitler!
Go back to your homes
and ranches quietly.
But I live
in a trailer.
Who's gonna
answer for...
What'd he say?
Louder, can't
hear you back here.
Let the sheriff
handle the Ferguson case.
Mob violence
isn't the answer.
Who's that guy
over there?
We've got to tell Cooper
that he's wrong, but we've
got to do it lawfully.
Flop drop at ten,
pass it on.
How do we know you
ain't in Cooper's pay?
-No, I'm not in Cooper's pay.
-Don't pick at that.
I'm not going to stand by and
watch a range war break out if
I can possibly help it.
Sam, you're talking
like a fool.
Cooper broke
his word!
Pay us and we
won't kill him.
-Yeah.
-He might listen to me.
He knows I don't' own a ranch,
so I have nothing personally
to gain.
At least let me try before
you all do something you might
all regret.
Go on back to
your ranches.
Give me a chance to
talk to Cooper alone.
Yeah, I got it down...
Real good deal, they
were having a special.
You know what he's
saying is horse sense.
Now why don't you
all go home?
You see where Oklahoma
wants to be a state?
Can you believe that?
Now there are acid burns all
over this part of the prairie.
Wait, everybody, this means we
have to go home to our wives!
Look at those
horses' asses.
I got your message.
I want to see your father.
I hope you two
will be very happy.
-I only want to talk to him.
-Here's your power drill.
I don't think
he'll see you.
Somebody's gotta make him
realize what's happening.
The small ranchers are up
in arms over the killing.
So this isn't a date?
I'd like to help.
For your sake.
Give me time to-- no!
Thank you.
He's the Lucas
Tanner of his time.
Had this meeting with
a bunch of cowboys today.
I think it went
pretty well.
You should
have seen me.
Made me honorary chair.
I'm good.
Still needs a Billy Jack or
a Gabby Hayes or a stretch
Armstrong or something.
This was my idea.
"Flintstones: The movie."
What do you think?
How long you gonna
keep this up?
As long as they keep
stealing my horses.
There's a law against
that, you know.
There's also a law about
giving a man a fair trial.
No there's not.
And not shooting him
down in cold blood.
They shouldn't have
resisted arrest.
Resist arrest.
That's just an excuse
for legalized murder.
Pete Ferguson didn't even have
a gun on him when he resisted
arrest.
Just the same, there were double
c horses found in that corral.
I still say a man is innocent
until he's proven guilty.
You would think that.
Call off your deputies.
Take back your mink.
I didn't start
this thing, barnum.
But now that it's started,
I'm going to finish it.
Where's the magic of
that cowboy meeting?
Damn.
Is that final?
That's final.
Double dog final.
So now nothing personal
about this on my part.
Here on in, it's
going to be different.
I'm going to make fun
of your condition.
That don't
scare me any.
See that he gets off the
range without being bothered.
Otherwise, I'm liable to
be accused of ambushing too.
Oh, she was gonna
let me see her nude.
What a reba.
Quit dabbing your
neck on my property!
My ears have been dripping
in this windy climate.
Ew! I'm not
touching it! Yuck!
Let's have a merchant
ivory sort of picnic.
What do you say?
I have to ride
back to St. Louis and
get a new hanky.
Could you pretend I'm not here
and taking your hat off?
Sorry it had
to be this way.
I gotta shoot you.
But he's wrong and
he's got to be shown.
He's all I have
in the world.
I love him in spite
of his faults.
-Yes, I know.
-You're evil
because of it.
That's why I want
it to be different.
Hey, this feels
good tighter.
-Sometimes things don't
work out the way you figure.
-What do you mean?
Oh, a guy will wander up
one range and down the other,
always looking for something
he thinks he can't find.
Like a second shirt!
And then suddenly
he'll stop at a spot.
Oh, it's cowboy poetry.
Aw, Ada Annie.
I guess I've said more
than I should have already.
No you haven't, Duke.
Touch my gingham.
Please go on.
Gimme that nude
head of yours!
Can't.
Being untrue to remedy.
So that's it for
my whole life, huh?
Yep.
Meanwhile, the bandana's out
there like a ticking bomb.
Every ranch, by strict zoning
law, must have parking for at
least five horses.
Did you know that?
-I didn't know that--
-shut up.
So you up for
some limbo?
Uh, I wouldn't
touch that.
Only one man has
this sweaty a neck.
This movie should have been
called "lost and found."
What a luck,
you found a hanky.
I wish I'd found a hanky,
I never find anything.
What's on the
program for tonight?
Oh, zig ziglar's
in town.
...so far.
So far?
But a couple of double c horses
found in his corral will prove
otherwise.
Go pick up rocky.
He's waiting for
you at the office.
-From zero to one in--
-...The whole thing.
You set me up!
-But then again...
-Keep it covered, Riley.
But, in fact, you
don't have to be...
To take advantage of
a man in a wheelchair.
Don't use your
wheelchair as a crutch.
-I'll kill you two
right where you stand.
-Well?
The right thing to do is to
keep you for the sheriff.
Jane.
Bring boy and cheetah.
Jane?
Jane has you
surrounded.
Uh, just as we planned,
Jane doesn't come when I call.
Jane!
Could you get
that for me?
What I mean is
I support your plan.
Why take the chance of
having it pinned on us.
Jane!
Stop this crazy thing!
Never mind, Jane.
You like the
coopers, don't you?
Don't you? Dukey likes
his coopers, doesn't he?
-She's pretty.
-So are you.
In a girly sort of way.
I'm not a girl.
I'm a woman,
a grown woman.
-I'll say.
-What's the matter...
Well, he-- that is,
i-- oh, never mind.
This muriatic acid
will-- ahh!
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
Oh darn.
I've been saving my own
filth for three weeks.
Well, I'll just have
to start over again.
Better get to it now.
I know it won't do
any good but some day i'm
gonna take a course in
female psychology.
May even become
a female!
Well, dad, doesn't your anxiety
about my leaving seem silly now?
Better tie it
better than that.
I can undo that knot.
I'll leave, I will,
I'm going...
Oh, how sweet, dad.
You're taking a little
nap on the lawn.
Looks like you got
some color, dad.
All right, hot wheels,
let's get going.
Well, no time
to talk, dad.
I'm going
straight upstairs.
I have a lot of
things to do today.
Dad, I want
to talk to you.
And don't say a word
till I'm finished.
Dad.
Daddy?
Dad?
Oh, good one, dad.
Oh, thanks a lot,
now I'm an orphan.
Dad!
Oh, not to worry,
that was me.
You mean you didn't
want that done?
Man, what a huge ear!
Look at that thing.
You apologize to
your daughter.
See what you
made her do?
Here, dry your tears
with this clue I planted.
Oh jeez, how long
is she gonna mourn?
It's not so much that he's dead,
it's just that I have
this headache.
I've seen this
bandana before.
It belongs
to Duke barnum.
See the neck sweat?
No.
No, he couldn't.
Why not?
I was with him.
I was at the edge
of the range.
After he left you, he must
have circled back here.
Come on, it's my plan,
play along.
Could have made it
back before you did.
Anyway, it smells
like antaeus.
That's his scent.
That settles it.
I'm going after
the sheriff.
I better put dad up on blocks
and leave him in the garage.
Baby, jeez.
♪♪
Get out of here.
This yours?
Oh boy,
who'd I kill now?
Yeah, thanks.
Must have dropped
it somewhere.
Over at
the double c, maybe?
Could be.
Why?
It'll probably
hang you.
Wow, they have really strict
littering laws around here.
That horse has
a Beatles wig.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Charlie Cooper.
Johnny pooper?
Who's that?
♪ Johnny pooper number
two bad man in the west ♪♪
Johnny pooper
also murdered.
Killed in his
own log cabin.
Good one.
Flash: Attractive
woman spotted.
Pooper held
as probe widens.
Barnum hires midgets
for defense team.
Jumbo to be witness
for prosecution.
Rose Kennedy
celebrates jubilee.
Knishes.
Get your old
west knishes.
Yep, you can go watch a wagon
wheel get made or we can go
to the trial.
It's crowd noise days in
Jacksonville at the milling
about festival.
Looks like the whole town's
turned out for the trial.
Should have
made t-shirts.
Can you get somebody
to defend Duke?
No, there ain't a lawyer in the
county wants to touch the case.
What will we do?
Looks like I go the...
I have a little law training.
You think you can?
I'll do my best.
Prosecutor's built
up a powerful case.
Shut up.
[All talking at once]
Cooper could get loose.
Call back auditions
for the Marlboro man.
That was a good
aa meeting.
Why would anyone be
sober in this town?
I'll see you inside.
Crack hits
the old west.
Guy on the far left,
nice curvy butt.
Long butt.
Whoo.
You been doing a lot
of drinking lately.
What's the matter?
Losing your nerve?
I can't help it.
-I'm Irish.
-Good one.
[Mumbling]
Town drunk's
a tough gig.
Keep seeing an old man who
sits there in his wheelchair.
You need to take a trip.
A long one.
I know a guy at
ask Mr. Foster.
Tell him I sent you.
Here, go drink
some more.
Don't come
back this way.
You are a beautiful man.
Everybody in this town's
a beautiful man.
Have a good time.
You all understand?
Sure.
You guys know him?
Anybody know him?
No idea.
Why did they have the
trial on the 48th floor?
You're employed as
a guard by the express company,
are you not?
-Guilty!
-Not yet.
Oh, sorry.
-On July 10th, while riding a
stagecoach into Jacksonville--
-you mean July.
You reported seeing a masked man
in the road through a pair of
field glasses, is that right?
That's right.
I saw him through
field glasses.
I was cowboy-watching.
Stand up,
put your hat on.
Now go stand
250 yards away.
Psst, wanna get
sequestered later?
Oh, wait a minute.
That ain't got anything
to do with the case.
So I object.
I'm only trying
to establish the charge
of the defendant, your honor.
Objection overruled.
Answer the question.
Is that the man?
Ruff, ruff!
He's having his
colors done.
Yes.
Would you say the man
you saw is a winter?
Please hold your applause
until all the testimony
has been given.
-Shemp.
-By the first he hit this
part of the country,
he shot one of
the double c men.
Semen.
Semen!
Thank you, thank you,
it was me who did it.
-Thank you.
-Keep the faith.
He's dead.
Duke barnum has been
a troublemaker ever since
he arrived.
Your bottom's been
a troublemaker?
He has repeatedly attacked my
men without any provocation.
Has the defendant Duke barnum
ever threatened your father
in your presence?
Take the curtain,
the curtain.
Hey, witness, hey.
She's a perjur.
Hey, witness.
Yeah, no.
Maybe, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Now he'll like me.
Maybe I am guilty.
We will now sing "a mighty
fortress is our god."
What is
the jury's verdict?
Uh, we weren't
listening, your honor.
Guilty, your honor.
Wait, they didn't say
I specifically was guilty.
I'm deputy dog.
-Hey.
-Deputy dog, hey.
You've been
a lousy client.
Here's that gun
you wan-- sorry.
Get going, sheriff,
get going.
Okay, there will be a 10-minute
break and the next sensational
trial will begin.
Huh?
12 pansy men.
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
That's a warehouse
in Newark.
Hold it, hold it, I've
always wanted to do this.
Ow!
That saved all
of two seconds.
Let's get him!
Can I get a ride
with you, Ted?
Ooh.
Oh, life is so hard
when you're stupid.
I wonder how that
could have happened?
Remedy, you're a national
friggin' treasure.
I wonder.
That's Hitchcock!
I want him brought in.
First they were mad, but
then they had to admit it was
pretty funny.
They should just close
this town and start over.
...in your mind before,
this proves that he's guilty.
Dr. Quinn, frontier
proctologist.
Isn't anybody
following me?
I thought I was a big
important criminal.
Don't know, just feels
like I forgot something.
Sir, why don't you put the gun
away before someone gets hurt?
Which was is the
territory, I wonder.
Well, heck, I'll just keep
going the way I was going.
I could have called Joel Hyatt,
but no, I go with remedy.
Procrastinating beaver.
--Duke?
Come on, Duke.
Have you done
your business?
-Did somebody
get back here?
-Duke!
It's remedy.
But kill him anyway.
I searched every
ranch in the valley.
They're headed
this way now.
-You got to be
moving on, Duke.
-Where to?
There's an old cave up in the
hills overlooking the path.
I used to hide there
when I was a little girl.
I don't think anybody
knows about it.
-I'll take you there.
-No, no, you better not.
If they should
spot me, I'd barely run around.
How do I get there?
Well, you cut across the south
end of the cuckoo ranch.
Wait, I'm lost,
start again.
-Follow that for about
a mile and then...
-Follow for a mile.
And then you get
shot by these guys.
I got a slipped disc, oh!
There goes the dumbest
cowboy you'll ever meet.
Where should
I bill you?
It's the night nazgul.
We're looking
for Duke barnum.
Have you seen him?
Okay.
Alternate universe manual.
Suppose we should
read the introduction?
Yeah.
So you die, captain,
and we all move up in rank.
You do not.
Get out of here.
"Welcome to the world
of alternate universes."
Crow has orders to
kill you, captain.
And he will
succeed, apparently.
Regrettable, but it will
leave me in command.
-Then I will exploit
the delithium crystal--
-Servo!
I can't wait to get him
back to his universe.
A little annoying.
You take a lot of chances.
So consider me for your
next corporate function.
I'm available for
all sorts of events.
Look, enough with
Joey the lemur.
Die, die, die,
die, die!
You know, this just might
be an alternate universe.
Well, duh.
Maybe they got
a computer down here.
Yeah.
Hey, computer?
[Voice]
Working.
Sounds like torgo!
[Voice]
Who?
Hey, computer.
-Working.
-Say, "the master."
The master.
That's great,
it sounds exactly like--
-Tom!
-Oh, right.
Uh, computer, are we
in an alternate universe?
[Voice]
Yes.
Well, how do
we get out?
[Voice] Get frank and forrester
to send back the matter
transference device.
-Say "the master" again.
-Belay that order.
Computer, would you put frank
and forrester on the screen,
please?
Ah, oh, right, remember,
you're the evil gypsy.
Oh, lord, I don't
know if I can...
Lord, they're still singing
that Joey the lemur song.
Hey, you knuckleheads.
Send down that matter
transference machine.
♪ Joey the lemur... ♪
oh, sure.
♪ Joey the lemur he
really is great ♪
♪ Joey... ♪♪
Ah! Wow!
All right, all right,
everybody here?
Nobody evil?
-Gypsy?
-Not evil.
I'm still not convinced
it happened.
Perhaps an
underdone potato,
or a bit of
undigested beef.
Let's check on the mads.
Oh, I feel so strange.
It's as if all my intestines
cried out at once and
were suddenly silenced.
Oh, but frank, look.
Someone left us
an agony booth.
-Me first!
-Race ya!
Let me in there.
♪♪
I, for one,
am glad you're back.
Me too.
What else happened?
Should have someone haul
away dad, I suppose.
Hey, it's the guy
who killed dad.
Yoo hoo!
Oh, mother blood!
You got some of my
tapes, I think.
I think you got "tusk" and
"larks' tongues in aspic."
We got a domestic in progress
over at the old Cooper place.
I love you!
What is it about you?
I don't need an
answer right away.
Her bullets say no but
her eyes say come hither.
Strange courting practices
of the old west--
shut up.
So I can't use
your bathroom?
Jane!
It's me, Duke!
I know that.
Oh.
Stand where you are
and drop your gun.
But, Jane, i--
oh, women.
Jeez, I'm having
a bad day.
Well, that's dating
in the 90s.
The 1890s.
It's not fair,
she had a bigger gun.
You know what, I'm really
not that mad at him.
Never brides,
always bridesmaids.
Now he's log oggilby.
Everything's up to
date in Kansas City.
Remedy, Duke's not
at the cave.
It doesn't look like
he's been there either.
Probably couldn't
find it in the dark.
I think I'll get in town,
see what I can find out.
You sure this will
make good toilet paper?
If you wait till my cake
raises, I'll go too.
"La cage aux folles,"
western style.
Cid!
El cid! Cid!
Go away,
nobody likes me.
Emerald city is closed.
He's hiding in an
abandoned stuckey's.
This shot's just screaming
out for a huge grasshopper
to appear.
Everybody is so stupid.
He could just go into town with
a fake moustache and no one
would notice.
That's not my horse.
I'm not here, go away.
Lucky, this hideout is
sometimes real crowded.
This place is
such a mess.
He should clean
up his hideout.
You hurt bad?
Oh, it's not too bad.
Just a flesh wound.
Touch it.
Then I'll go get remedy.
Soon as he gets back,
we'll get you out of here.
I've been thinking
about that.
-Oh, lower.
-I want to stay here.
This is the last place in
the world they'd think
of looking for me.
He's in here!
Oh.
Yuck.
Stuff makes me sneeze.
Hay fever, I guess.
Remedy must have
a remedy for that.
We'll bring some
back for you.
Great scene, huh?
Wow.
This movie has more scenes of
people picking at themselves.
Just do a little morning bowl,
then get to work.
No, you can't
have any.
This is $80 an ounce.
Put a towel
under the door.
So you wanna walk across
the street to Fenway
and catch a game?
Rocky tells me that my men
are no longer deputies.
-Again?
-That's right, Riley.
The way things have quieted
down, the double c don't need
-any more deputies.
-Nice tobaccy aroma.
Is that field
and stream?
What about Duke barnum?
Oh, we can handle him
when we catch him.
Yep.
I figured my boys could
help you out there.
Would you stop
touching yourself there?
Riley.
This could be the start
of a beautiful friendship.
Duke barnum was convicted
legally and he's gonna
hang legally too.
But I aim to see that
he's brought in alive.
You pothead.
Go listen to some
big bamboo, huh?
Well, rotator
cuff feels good.
Think I'll be ready for
my start on Thursday.
Me again.
Where were you yesterday?
Brought you some
swaddling clothes.
A purse, thank you!
Wanna play
some marbles?
...beginning to get
on my nerves.
Oh, another day or two and
it'll be as good as new.
Ha, green sleeves.
Better bring me a fresh
supply of those pills.
I'll pick 'em up in town
tomorrow when I go for my mail.
What's been going on?
Well, this Cooper thing sort of
put an end to all that fighting.
The coy remedy.
Let's fill the canteen
with brown mustard.
Funny thing happened
the other morning.
A priest and
a rabbi walk-- oh.
Riley Morgan took over the
Ferguson ranch and...
Ranch and three
other places.
Well, you probably
ought to get going.
He picked up some
notes at the bank.
Notes... notes.
Dead men's notes.
I know what you mean,
but we ain't got no proof.
Well.
Ever done
it in the hay?
...pills tomorrow night.
My crotch is
suddenly cold.
'Lo, Cal.
Lo-Cal?
Hiya, remedy.
This stuff sure
accumulates.
Especially when
you don't deliver it.
Oh, uh, gonna be anywhere
near the double c?
Why?
Drop this letter off
for Riley Morgan.
Save me a trip.
Sure.
If you don't, I might
become disgruntled.
♪ Bless this
beautiful day ♪♪
It's a letter,
it doesn't rattle.
Let's see here:
"Dear sir, your horse has
a potentially serious
design flaw which can
result in explosion
and fire," hmm.
"Betty some morphine Jack will
have the Mike killed Casper."
Us post office.
There's still no cheaper way
to deliver a blackmail threat.
Why it's general delivery,
one of the great generals
of the civil war.
He's covering the stamp
so we can't see it has
Roosevelt on it.
So I get three
free cds now?
Oh, they should call
the movie "butterfingers."
Ungodly coincidences
of the old west.
He dropped something,
see what it is.
It's a plot device.
It's very flimsy,
so be careful.
Just a couple of letters.
I'll just read
'em with my feet.
Hey, this
one's for you.
It's from Hank Davis.
I don't know
any Hank Davis.
Let me see that.
Guilty valley.
Guilty, California.
Oh, shoot, there was
probably gum in here.
He always sends me some.
Come on, I want
that letter.
We'll head him
off at exit 31c!
I don't want to see
another horse chase!
Stop it.
I didn't read
the letter, go away.
That's it, I'm going
to vaudeville.
Let's see, what's the
stupidest thing I can do?
Great tune.
Ooh, he's got one of
them amphibious horses.
This is no place
for a gelding!
Maybe they're like bees and
they won't go in the water.
Sure enough.
♪♪
Wait till he gets
to the middle.
It's good and deep there.
I'm on goul.
Watch this.
Right in the butt.
Fortunately, remedy's taken a
correspondence scuba course.
A little bit of
Jacksonville died that day.
He was anxious
to get somewhere.
I've got a pretty good hunch
what was in that letter.
But it's where no
one will see it now.
-Except maybe fishes.
-I'm sick of your carping.
I think you and I better ride
over to red bluff next week and
fix Hank so he doesn't write any
more letters.
I thought we were gonna
have our camping holiday.
People just wander from
scene to scene in this movie.
-Cid! El cid!
-Cid!
Solar panels.
Let's make a statement
with a roof in this design.
In Wisconsin, that barn would
say "diesel cheese gifts."
Early carhops...
I thought you were Dale.
Hey, you shouldn't
come here so often.
Somebody might see you.
I have to take care
of remedy's patient.
And I need the child
support payment.
You've got to
get out of here.
If they find you,
they'll kill you.
I can't keep
hiding forever.
Besides, if I leave,
I'll never prove anything.
Does he just sit in there and
plan golf courses in his mind?
Boy, just sit back
and they roll right in.
Pretend she's not here.
I'll have a horse waiting for
you as soon as it gets dark.
Would you like cornbread
or coleslaw with that?
You'll help
me get away?
Yes.
Oh, I'm gonna
French your hat.
I'd never leave knowing you
think I killed your father.
But I killed
your father.
-Somehow I feel you're innocent
and I'll never forgive--
-the mummy!
Remedy!
Worse.
Got me...
Sucking at my skin.
Is it wrong that
I'm glad about this?
I think those women did the
right thing by not wearing
earrings with those outfits.
Over accessorizing.
Right.
Ew, he blew his
nose on that thing.
Get rid of it.
The juice of two lemons...
What is this?
Take this
to the sheriff.
You stay here with him.
Oh thank you.
I'll babysit the wet,
bloody, stinky remedy.
If the horse drops
below 50, it will explode.
"Speed", whoo!
El cid's making
good time.
Come on, I'll
buy you a drink.
Let me call Ripley's.
Hey.
I'm not guilty,
everyone!
-Get him!
-Kill him!
Get him!
♪ Oldtown town
looks the same ♪♪
Ah, Jacksonville.
Hey, he changed
his shirt.
Must be a disguise.
Don't pick at that,
don't...
Ching, ching, ching,
ching, ching...
Not even time for
a quick scotch?
I hope he kills the
apple dumpling gang.
What's that
thing you say?
Grab, no.
-Push.
-Uh...
We know who killed
Charlie Cooper, Riley.
Who's Charlie
Cooper Riley?
Now you know
what I meant.
I'm settling
a personal matter first.
Got a package to pick
up over at the sears.
Get off me, you load.
Hey, he never
got his drink.
Hey, wait, I wanted to tell
you who killed that guy.
This is the funny part,
it was you.
Listen, when
a man's gotta go.
There's a hooverville
in this town.
Hey!
That's the last straw.
Oh.
You're too late, I have an
informal agreement with the
owners.
You're mad,
aren't you?
I can tell you're mad.
Uh, just don't
tickle me.
I'm thin and it
wouldn't be fair.
That door's the only
way out of here.
That's brave talk
for a man pointing a gun.
Hey, I'm just telling
you where the door is.
Just kind of fyi, no reason
to get all made at me.
That's right, Riley.
Yep.
I'll give you a better break
than you gave Cooper.
I'll give you the
first seven punches.
Kicks, too.
Uh, we already saw this
so can we be excused?
Albert glasser wanted to do
his best work for this scene
and unfortunately,
he did.
Comfortable place
for a fight, anyway.
You'll do anything to get
me into leather, won't you?
So did they call them
western saddles back then?
Hmm.
That's a poser.
Please, I've already
got hay in my pants.
Away in a murder,
no crib for a death.
The cattle are dying.
Okay.
Hey, pancho.
Hey, Cisco.
Would you two keep your
fight on the lower level?
We're filming "the rifleman"
up here.
I still hope they kill
the apple dumpling gang.
The air is thinner up here,
so I think that means the skinny
guy has an advantage.
I'm-- smell my hand!
It's baron
Von raschke!
Oh, found the needle.
See?
Just proves
you did it.
This is about more than
just murder and blackmail
between these two.
Just think, right now, the
townspeople are getting uglier,
stupider and they're
dropping things.
This scene disturbed me at
the beginning of the movie,
but now it makes me happy.
You never should have
butted into this in
the first place, barnum.
Now I'm going
to finish you.
Oh, he's got a cute
little blood moustache.
Usually when this guy kills
people, he makes them
go get the belt.
-Ah!
What just happened?
They felt off
the hash browns.
Oh, I had a huge skeleton
key in my front pocket.
Owie.
No, stay here.
I'll make us breakfast.
Tu es incredible,
partner.
That's French, partner.
Oh, that didn't help.
Now the bowling ball's gonna
roll down on his head.
I fought the loft
and the loft won.
Oh man.
Sorry.
Well, everything's
better now.
Doc says my spine
just healed right up.
It was amazing.
-Hi, Terry.
-You're dirt.
Hi, Jane.
How's the patient?
Oh, he's been...
For days.
Look at him now.
It's mcgreets!
That's some fancy-looking
suit he's wearing.
He won't tell me why, but he
bought it special for today.
Getting shot was the best thing
that ever happened to him.
-Hello, remedy.
-I'm not reading "hustler!"
Another mail
order course?
Well, I had to do something
while I was laying on my back
for two months.
Whoa.
What kind of
a course was this one?
Oh, you'll see.
Mailman get here yet?
I'm expecting something
awful important.
Remedy is now
completely psychotic.
Oh, there he is.
Well, the Wells Fargo wagon
is coming down the street.
I have to go to
the lampart bank.
We're spreading the word
of no sex or alcohol.
It's Stalin
with Svetlana.
At least curly won't have
to wear a dress anymore.
This came for
you today, remedy.
Oh no.
This?
This is really creepy.
I've been taking
a mail order course...
This lesson calls
for a model.
So they sent me one.
Oh god, please
protect me.
Remedy, there are laws.
Hello, curly.
-I wonder how--
-oh, ram it, clown.
-Really.
-Yes, let's close
with another
random assortment of notes,
courtesy of Albert glasser.
-Mike, would you mind
telling me what happened?
-Yeah.
Well, sure, you see, the mads
sent up the matter transference
device during an ion storm.
Dumb thing
to do, right?
'Cause it sent Tom Servo and
our own lovable gypsy into an
alternate universe whilst
your evil doppelgangers
were sent into ours.
Oh, is that
all it was?
You know, gang, I think about
one trip a year to an alternate
universe is enough for me.
It wasn't that
funny, was it?
That's all right.
Let's read this
letter though, that might--
-hi, guys.
-Oh, hi.
Say, frank and I figured out a
way that we can communicate from
our satellite of love to your
satellite of love.
So we thought we'd
stop by and say hi.
Hi!
As a matter of fact, we've
prepared a little song for you.
We hope you like it.
It goes a little
something like this.
♪ Joey the lemur... ♪
I hate to stop you.
Hate like the world to do it,
we have to read a letter.
Or we get punished
or some such thing.
Yeah, we get punished.
Anyway, here it is.
It's from
Joseph a. Holzman.
Put it on still
store there, cambot.
Joseph's from
kailua, Hawaii.
Ah, yes.
In our world, we
also have a Hawaii.
And many
similar places.
Your Massachusetts, your
Illinois, your zeelaclamees.
Yeah, that's great.
The letter begins,
"dear Mike and the bots.
We really enjoy your show on
oceanic cable channel 30."
Ah yes.
In our world, we too have cable
television where we enjoy many
similar programs to yours.
Your "I love Lucy",
your "home improvement,"
your "my mother, my
collostacollucacollostaka
le ek i- -"
letter concludes by saying um,
"anyway, keep up the riffs..."
Ah yes.
In our world,
we too have riffs.
We listen to many forms of
popular music such as your Louis
Armstrong, you're the Beatles,
your zylark blues band
from omnicron city three.
Well, we're sorry
you have to go.
Bye bye.
[All talking at once]
-Wow.
-In a way, really, it's kind
of comforting to know that,
uh, no matter what
universe you're
from, you can still
be really annoying.
Amen to that.
Oh.
Oh!
[Laughing]
Oh yes.
♪♪